https://www.irsaway.com/privacy-policy/

Contact Us
Please take a moment to review our privacy policy.
What information do we collect?
We, Joseph M. Arndt, III, P. A. collect information from you when you fill out a “contact us” form.
If you contact us using the online form, you will be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number and personal information regarding your potential case. You may, however, visit our site anonymously, which means without providing this information.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information that you send to us will be used for providing legal guidance and assistance.
Your information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever without your consent other than for the express purpose of delivering the service requested.
Do we use cookies?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer?s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow), enabling the site?s or service provider?s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, transfer to outside parties or otherwise allow access to your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website because those parties agree in writing to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe that its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others? rights, property or safety.
Non-personally identifiable visitor information, however, may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.
Non-personally identifiable visitor information may include: which pages on the site are accessed, what information is downloaded, what type of browser and operating system are being used, which Internet service provider is being used, and other information of this general nature may be collected about visitors to the site. This information does not allow us to personally identify the site visitor. By collecting this information, we learn how to best develop our website to meet the needs and desires of our visitors.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party resources on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Online Privacy Policy only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Email Opt-out If you wish to no longer receive email correspondence from Joseph M. Arndt, III please send an email with Unsubscribe? in the subject line.
Terms and conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://irsaway.com/disclaimer/
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our website privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Steer Clear of These IRS Audit Red Flags!
Hiring a Tax Attorney? Questions to Consider
Do I Need a Tax Lawyer?
